Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The wind once paused by the rain streaked window♪
♪توقفت الرياح ذات مرة عند النافذة التي لطختها قطرات المطر♪
♪Sketching you in gentle strokes♪
♪أرسمك بخطوط رقيقة♪
♪From the old town, cooking smoke curled upward♪
♪من البلدة القديمة، تصاعد دخان الطهي♪
♪Smoothing the tide of my restless thoughts♪
♪تهدئة موجة أفكاري المضطربة♪
=A Vow in the Dark=
=عهد في الظلام=
=Episode 1=
=الحلقة 1=
(Fengling Sea)
(بحر فنغلينغ)
(Hong Zhua, God of War of the Immortal Realm)
(هونغ تشوا، إله الحرب في عالم الخلود)
(Jin Li, Demon subduing Immortal)
(جين لي، الخالد الذي يُخضع الشياطين)
Greeting, Hong Zhua.
تحياتي، هونغ تشو.
Sorry for being late.
أعتذر عن التأخير.
Jin Li,
جين لي,
you've been lurking in the Demon Realm for years.
لقد كنت تتربص في عالم الشياطين لسنوات.
Have you found a way to vanquish the Demon Clan?
هل وجدت طريقة للقضاء على عشيرة الشياطين؟
This is the Demon Defense Array of the Demon Realm.
هذا هو نظام الدفاع الشيطاني لعالم الشياطين.
Good.
جيد.
With the Array,
باستخدام المصفوفة،
we can wipe out the Demon Clan.
بإمكاننا القضاء على عشيرة الشياطين.
Jin Li,
جين لي,
the time has come.
لقد حان الوقت.
You'll have
سيكون لديك
to execute Jie Chuan,
لإعدام جي تشوان،
Demon Sovereign.
سيد الشياطين.
Jin Li,
جين لي,
why did you deceive me?
لماذا خدعتني؟
(Jie Chuan, Demon Sovereign)
(جي تشوان، ملك الشيطان)
Jin Li,
جين لي,
you betrayed me.
لقد خنتني.
Is everything we shared
هل كل ما شاركناه هو
in the past all a lie?
هل كان كل شيء في الماضي مجرد كذبة؟
Jin Li,
جين لي,
the immortal and demon realms can never coexist.
لا يمكن لعوالم الخالدين والشياطين أن تتعايش أبدًا.
Do it.
افعلها.
Jin Li,
جين لي,
do not forget your mission.
لا تنس مهمتك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Sorry?
آسف؟
Even if it costs you body and soul,
حتى لو كلف ذلك جسدك وروحك،
you still intend to kill me?
هل ما زلت تنوي قتلي؟
My love for you is sincere.
حبي لك صادق.
But killing you
لكن قتلك
is my fate.
هذا قدري.
I have to betray you.
عليّ أن أخونك.
May we never meet again.
عسى ألا نلتقي مجدداً.
Jin LI!
جين لي!
(I'm willing)
(أنا مستعد)
(to trade all our memories)
(لتبادل كل ذكرياتنا)
(for one trace of your soul to remain.)
(ليبقى أثر واحد من روحك.)
(From this moment on,)
(من هذه اللحظة فصاعدًا،)
(I shall be sealed forever)
(سأُختم إلى الأبد)
(in the Void Land beyond the Three Realms.)
(في أرض الفراغ الواقعة وراء العوالم الثلاثة.)
(We shall never meet again)
(لن نلتقي مرة أخرى)
(All that has happened)
(كل ما حدث)
(shall end here today.)
(سينتهي الأمر هنا اليوم.)
(Everything's over.)
(انتهى كل شيء.)
All has been shaped by fate and fortune.
لقد تشكل كل شيء بفعل القدر والحظ.
Since Jin Li has chosen you,
بما أن جين لي قد اختارك،
you shall nurture Jin Li's soul.
عليك أن ترعى روح جين لي.
From this day forth,
ابتداءً من هذا اليوم فصاعداً،
you are my disciple.
أنت تلميذي.
I shall call you
سأتصل بك
Ji Li.
جي لي.
(300 years later)
(بعد مرور 300 عام)
(Ji Li, Immortal Beast)
(جي لي، الوحش الخالد)
(Jie Chuan and Jin Li)
(جي تشوان وجين لي)
(used their flesh and blood to form this Hybrid Tree.)
(استخدموا لحمهم ودمائهم لتشكيل هذه الشجرة الهجينة.)
(It blooms and bears fruit only once every three centuries.)
(لا تزهر وتثمر إلا مرة واحدة كل ثلاثة قرون.)
(The Spirit Fruit can grant a thousand years of cultivation,)
(يمكن لثمرة الروح أن تمنح ألف عام من الزراعة،)
(bestowing an eternal form.)
(منح شكلاً أبدياً.)
Spirit Fruit,
فاكهة الروح،
my master spent most of his cultivation
أمضى سيدي معظم وقته في التدريب
to turn me from a fish into human.
لتحويلي من سمكة إلى إنسان.
Today, you shall fall.
اليوم ستسقطون.
I'm going to take you back
سأعيدك إلى الوراء
to celebrate my master's birthday.
للاحتفال بعيد ميلاد أستاذي.
(Void Land)
(أرض فارغة)
It chills to the touch.
يبرد عند لمسه.
This is the Frost Blossom.
هذه زهرة الصقيع.
They say
يقولون
it only appears in the Void Land.
لا يظهر إلا في أرض الفراغ.
This is the Void Land.
هذه هي أرض الفراغ.
The Void Land
أرض الفراغ
has been hidden away for years.
لقد تم إخفاؤه لسنوات.
Now,
الآن،
even a weak immortal
حتى الخالد الضعيف
can freely come here?
هل يمكن لأحد أن يأتي إلى هنا بحرية؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
You don't deserve to know.
أنت لا تستحق أن تعرف.
What is your name?
ما اسمك؟
Are you from the Speech Clan?
هل أنت من عشيرة الكلام؟
My master once told me
قال لي سيدي ذات مرة
the Speech Clan can seize souls
بإمكان عشيرة الكلام الاستيلاء على الأرواح
by knowing one's name.
بمعرفة اسم الشخص.
Speech Clan?
عشيرة الكلام؟
They're timid in nature
إنهم خجولون بطبيعتهم
and poor in their arts.
وفقراء في فنونهم.
In the great war 300 years ago,
في الحرب العظمى قبل 300 عام،
countless immortals perished
هلك عدد لا يحصى من الخالدين
to subdue the Demon Clan,
لإخضاع عشيرة الشياطين،
which left their spirits
مما ترك أرواحهم
drifting outside,
الانجراف في الخارج،
unable to be found.
لم يتم العثور عليه.
Are you one of them?
هل أنت واحد منهم؟
Noisy.
صاخب.
Such a massive ice spike
نتوء جليدي ضخم كهذا
is stuck here for three centuries.
عالق هنا منذ ثلاثة قرون.
Doesn't it hurt?
ألا يؤلمك ذلك؟
(Hall of the Demon Realm)
(قاعة عالم الشياطين)
(Sunlight Hall of the Immortal Realm)
(قاعة ضوء الشمس في عالم الخلود)
This is bad.
هذا سيء.
I can sense it.
أستطيع أن أشعر بذلك.
That power is Demonic Ether.
تلك القوة هي الأثير الشيطاني.
(Luo Cha)
(لو تشا)
It must be my brother.
لا بد أنه أخي.
Heed my command.
أطع أمري.
Soon,
قريباً،
we shall welcome Jie Chuan back to his throne.
سنرحب بعودة جي تشوان إلى عرشه.
Yes.
نعم.
Who exactly are you?
من أنت بالضبط؟
With such meager spiritual power,
بهذه القوة الروحية الضئيلة،
why were you able to awaken the ice spike?
لماذا تمكنت من إيقاظ شوكة الجليد؟
For 300 years,
لمدة 300 عام،
I've tried every possible way,
لقد جربت كل الطرق الممكنة،
yet none have succeeded.
لكن لم ينجح أحد.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
ليس لدي أدنى فكرة عما تتحدث عنه.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
Can you pull the ice spike out
هل يمكنك سحب مسمار الجليد؟
and free me from this?
وتخلصني من هذا؟
Free you?
هل أنت حر؟
Are you an immortal or a demon?
هل أنت خالد أم شيطان؟
Do you need to rank
هل تحتاج إلى تصنيف؟
the worth of saving someone?
ما قيمة إنقاذ شخص ما؟
If I'm not an immortal,
إن لم أكن خالداً،
would you refuse to help?
هل سترفض المساعدة؟
I don't divide lives into ranks.
أنا لا أقسم الأرواح إلى مراتب.
Nor do I judge by clan.
ولا أحكم على الناس بناءً على عشيرتهم.
But I at least need to know.
لكنني على الأقل بحاجة إلى معرفة ذلك.
What if you turn out
ماذا لو اتضح أنك
to be a cruel demon?
أن تكون شيطاناً قاسياً؟
(If she learns my true identity,)
(إذا علمت هويتي الحقيقية،)
(I fear...)
(أخشى...)
Immortal Beast,
الوحش الخالد،
you're smart.
أنت ذكي.
I was once
كنت ذات مرة
an immortal in the great war.
خالد في الحرب العظمى.
I was gravely wounded
لقد أصبت بجروح خطيرة
and trapped here for many years,
وبقينا عالقين هنا لسنوات عديدة،
endured endless torment.
تحمل عذاباً لا ينتهي.
You are
أنت
an immortal?
خالد؟
Why do you carry no trace of immortal aura?
لماذا لا تحمل أي أثر لهالة الخلود؟
You are
أنت
quite cautious.
حذر للغاية.
I was sealed
لقد تم ختمي
by the ice spike here.
بجوار نتوء الجليد هنا.
Now,
الآن،
I only have
ليس لدي سوى
a bit spiritual power in my palm,
قليل من القوة الروحية في كفّي،
not enough to break the seal.
لا يكفي لكسر الختم.
You truly are an immortal.
أنت حقاً خالد.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I'll save you.
سأنقذك.
Don't pull it out.
لا تخلعها.
Master, I'm saving an immortal.
يا سيدي، أنا أنقذ خالداً.
Seal that ice spike back.
أغلق مسمار الجليد بإحكام.
Master, look.
يا سيدي، انظر.
He's not an immortal.
إنه ليس خالداً.
He's Jie Chuan, Demon Sovereign.
إنه جي تشوان، ملك الشياطين.
Hong Zhua.
هونغ تشو.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
♪Thin wisps of smoke weave through the river♪
♪خيوط رقيقة من الدخان تتسلل عبر النهر♪
♪Melodies and wine fade, drunk beneath the sunset♪
تتلاشى الألحان والنبيذ، ونحن نُشرب تحت غروب الشمس.
♪Lonely light and sword shadow sway the falling leaves♪
♪ضوء وحيد وظل سيف يتمايلان مع الأوراق المتساقطة♪
♪Laughing at my recklessness in this life♪
أضحك على تهوّري في هذه الحياة
♪You come to me in every way♪
♪تأتون إليّ بكل الطرق♪
♪Filling my dreams with tangled love and hate♪
♪أملأ أحلامي بمزيج من الحب والكراهية♪
♪All my best years were for you♪
♪كل أجمل سنوات عمري كانت من أجلك♪
♪At the far edge of the world where lanterns fade♪
♪على الحافة البعيدة للعالم حيث تخبو الفوانيس♪
♪Through the mortal dust, time flows with its trials♪
♪عبر غبار الفناء، يتدفق الزمن بمحنه♪
♪Joys and sorrows ease grief♪
♪الأفراح والأحزان تخفف من وطأة الحزن♪
♪At dusk, petals fall as winter snow carries the starlight♪
♪عند الغسق، تتساقط البتلات بينما يحمل ثلج الشتاء ضوء النجوم♪
♪Across endless lifetimes, the ballad endures♪
♪عبر أجيال لا حصر لها، تبقى الأغنية خالدة♪